winnerdownloadmanager.com 2014-06-26

# Winner Download Manager - Privacy policy

Winner Solutions LLC respects the privacy of all of our users and is committed to protecting such privacy in accordance with this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy document explains our treatment of your personally identifiable information collected in connection with your activities on this Website and related to Winner Download Manager product 

  1. ### Web browser cookies

Our Site may use "cookies" to enhance User experience. User's web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly. 

  2. ### Non-personal identification information

We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site and Winner Download Manager. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information. 

  3. ### How we use collected information

Winner Solutions LLC may collect and use Users personal information for the following purposes: 

    * \- To improve customer service   
Information you provide helps us respond to your customer service requests and support needs more efficiently. 
    * \- To improve our Site and Winner Download Manager   
We may use feedback you provide to improve our products and services. 
  4. ### Sharing your personal information

We do not sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above. 

  5. ### Changes to this policy

Winner Solutions LLC may occasionally update this Privacy Policy. Any changes will be posted to this site, so we encourage you to continuously review our Privacy Policy. 

  6. ### Contact information

For questions regarding this Privacy Policy please email Winner Solutions LLC at
